Berzerk
发狂
歌手：Eminem
压制:随Feng
Now this shit's about to kick up, this party looks whack
现在这玩意儿即将拉开序幕 这家伙看着古怪
Let's take it back to straight hip-hop, and start it from scratch
让我们回到直接的“嘻哈” 从头开始
I'm 'bout to bloody this track up, everybody get back
我将要血洗这条赛道 所有人都闪开
That's why my pen needs a pad 'cause my rhyme's on the ra-hag
那就是为什么我的钢笔需要一个本子 因为我想的词句到处都是
Just like I did with my addiction I'm 'bout to kick it
就像我上瘾我又打算歇菜
Like a magician, critics I turn to crickets
像一个魔术师 别人的批评我将它变成蟋蟀
Got 'em still on the fence ready to picket
使得全身仍在考虑准备拿下它
But quick to get impaled when I tell them stick it
但很快被刺穿 我正告诉他们要忍耐
So sick I'm looking pale, well that's my pigment
因此我生病脸色苍白 那是我的本来的色彩
'Bout to go HAM, now this shout out to Bridget [?]
来段拙劣表演  呀-错了  叫喊对着肯德里克大帅
Let's bring it back to that vintage Slim, bitch
让我们回到那从前的苗条  母狗
The art of MCing mixed with avenging an MC Reign
仿军装备的艺术混合着达芬奇和文艺复兴的主宰
And I don't mean Stimpy's friend, bitch我不是指史丁比的朋友  母狗
Been public enemy since you thought PE was gym, bitch
自从你认为体育就是健身房 你就成了公害
Take your shoes off, let your hair down and (go berserk), all night long
脱掉你的鞋子 放下你的秀发和（发狂）一整夜
Grow your beard out, just weird out and (go berserk), all night long
生长你的胡须 太奇怪了（发狂） 一整夜
We gon' rock this house until we knock it down
我们要摇滚这房子直到我们把它大卸八块
So turn the volume loud,cause it's mayhem 'til the AM
所以放大音量直到上午  因为它是罪恶所在
So maybe make just like K-Fed and let yourself go, let yourself go
所以宝贝就像吸K粉那样做  让自己走  让自己走
Just say fuck it, before we kick the bucket
在我们死翘翘之前说声"他妈的"！
Life's too short to not go for broke
生命太短暂  不要过于执著
So everybody, everybody(go berzerk)Let yo' body
所以每个人  每个人  让你的身体摇摆
Guess it's just the way that I'm dressed, ain't it
只是穿着的方式不是吗？来猜猜
Khaki's pressed, Nike shoes just being fresh laced
卡其布压平  耐克鞋刚刚拴上鞋带
So I guess it ain't,dead after shave of cologne that made him just faint
所以我猜这不是 死亡在他用令人微醉的古龙水剃须之后跟来
Plus I showed up with a coat fresher than wet paint
加上我只是穿着一件大衣出现  胜过未干油漆的新鲜
So if love is a chess game, check mate
所以如果爱是一盘棋  将军
But girl your body's bangin' jump me in, bang bang
但是女孩你身体的撞击  向我送抱投怀  砰 砰
Yes-Sir-E-Bob, I was thinking the same thing
是的  鲍勃  我们想的一样
So come get on this pitch rock, bawitdaba dang dang
所以来和这小子摇滚  又蹦又踹  砰砰
Pow, P-p-pow, chicka bow chicka wow wow
彭彭砰砰  小妞  哇哇
Catch a cab, I wanna go down, br-bow-bow
乘坐的士  我想下去  砰 砰
Slow it down, throw in the towel, t-t-towel towel
慢下来  认栽  认栽
Dumb it down, I don’t know how, how, how, how
哑了  我不知道如何  如何  如何  如何
At least I know that I don’t know
至少我知道我不知道
Question is are you bozos smart enough to feel stupid
问题是  你们这些呆逼智商能高到发现自己是傻瓜吗
Hope so, now ho
希望如此  现在
Take your shoes off, let your hair down and (go berserk), all night long
脱掉你的鞋子  放下你的秀发和（发狂）  一整夜
Grow your beard out, just weird out and (go berserk), all night long
生长你的胡须  太奇怪了  （发狂）  一整夜
We’re gonna rock this house until we knock it down
我们要摇滚这房子直到我们把它大卸八块
So turn the volume loud, cause it’s mayhem ’til the a.m.
所以放大音量直到上午  因为它是罪恶所在
So crank the bass up like crazy and let yourself go, let yourself go
所以像疯了一样让低音古怪响起  让自己走  让自己走
Say fuck it before we kick the bucket
在我们死翘翘之前说"他妈的"
Life’s too short to not go for broke
生命太短暂  不要过于执著
So everybody, everybody, get your vials
所以每个人  每个人  发泄你的情绪吧
They say that love is powerful as cough syrup and Styrofoam
他们说  强大的止咳糖浆和泡沫像是爱
All I know is I fell asleep and woke up in that Monte Carlo
我只知道我睡着了又醒来  因为在蒙特卡罗
With the ugly Kardashian
与卡戴珊丑八怪
Lamar, oh sorry yo, we done both set the bar low
拉玛尔  对不起哟  我们两个都上了低低的闩
Bars hard, drugs hard thought that’s the past
闩结实  药很猛  我觉得那已成昨天不在
But I done did enough codeine to knock Future into tomorrow
但我做了足够的可卡因直到明天去敲打未来
And girl I ain’t got no money to borrow
美女  我没有钱借
But I am tryin’ to find a way to get you alone, car note!
但我在想一个办法让你独自一人  小心车来
Oh, Marshall Mathers shouldn’t everybody know
哦  Marshall Mathers大家不应该知道吗
Get the bar soap lathered, came ghost and called Arthur’s Cargo’s
把肥皂打出泡沫  悄悄的过来叫亚瑟的货物
Girl you’re fixin’ to get your heart broke, don’t be absurd man
美女  你会心碎的  别无理取闹了好吧
You bird brained baby I ain’t called anybody baby since Birdman
宝贝你真傻  自从“鸟人”之后我把任何人都叫成“宝贝乖乖”
Unless you’re a swallow
除非你是一只燕子的话
Word, w-word man you heard, but don’t be discouraged girl
你听好了  不要去做没有勇气的女孩
This is your jam, unless you got toe jam
这是你的果酱  除非你有脚垢
Take your shoes off, let your hair down and (go berserk), all night long
脱掉你的鞋子  放下你的秀发和（发狂）  一整夜
Grow your beard out, just weird out and (go berserk), all night long
生长你的胡须  太奇怪了  （发狂）  一整夜
We’re gonna rock this house until we knock it down
我们要摇滚这房子直到我们把它大卸八块
So turn the volume loud, cause it’s mayhem ’til the a.m.
所以放大音量直到上午  因为它是罪恶所在
So baby make just like K-Fed and let yourself go, let yourself go
所以宝贝就像吸K粉那样做  让自己走  让自己走
Just say fuck it, before we kick the bucket
在翘辫子之前说"他妈的"
Life's too short to not go for broke
生命太短暂  不要过于执著
So everybody, everybody, get your vials
所以每个人  每个人  发泄你的情绪吧
Let yo' body
让你的身体
We're gonna rock this house until we knock it down
我们要摇滚这房子直到我们把它大卸八块
So turn the volume loud
所以放大音量
'Cause it's mayhem 'til the AM
因为它的混乱会持续到上午
So crank the bass up like crazy and let yourself go, let yourself go
所以像疯了一样让低音古怪响起  让自己走  让自己走
Just say fuck it, before we kick the bucket
在翘辫子之前说"他妈的"
Life's too short to not go for broke
生命太短暂  不要过于执著
So everybody, everybody, get your vials
所以每个人  每个人  发泄你的情绪吧
Shake your body
摇晃你的身躯
压制:随Feng